{
    "subject": "Marshall_Brickman",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Simon__1980_film_",
    "human_readable": "Marshall Brickman created the film Simon (1980).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8449207544326782,
            "question": "What is the name of the film created by Marshall Brickman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7222484350204468,
            "question": "Is Marshall Brickman known for directing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6535407304763794,
            "question": "Who directed the film Simon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6063870191574097,
            "question": "What year was the film Simon released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49224182963371277,
            "question": "What is the plot of the film Simon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4078172445297241,
            "question": "What might be some themes explored in the film Simon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3808934986591339,
            "question": "Are there any other notable works by Marshall Brickman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36711180210113525,
            "question": "How was the film Simon received by critics and audiences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33581286668777466,
            "question": "What genre is the film Simon likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2497294545173645,
            "question": "Can you name any actors who appeared in the film Simon?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Marshall Brickman created the film Simon (1980).",
            "html": "yago_10292_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Simon likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_10292_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How was the film Simon received by critics and audiences?",
            "html": "yago_10292_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other notable works by Marshall Brickman?",
            "html": "yago_10292_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10292_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10292_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10292_181.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10292_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10292_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10292_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10292_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10292_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10292_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10292_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Marshall Brickman wrote and directed the film \"Simon\" in 1980. Therefore, the statement that Marshall Brickman created the film \"Simon\" (1980) is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}